const quiz = [
    {
        question: "I wanna rock and roll all night...",
        answerChoices: [
            "... and sleep til noon!",
            "... just kidding, I don't rock or roll.",
            "... and party every day!",
            "... I can raise and lower my cholesterol at will.",
        ],
        correctAnswer: "... and party every day!",
        feedback: "I hope you got this one right, because the next few won't be so easy!"
    },

    {
        question: 'How many strings total does a guitar usually have?',
        answerChoices: [
            "4",
            "5",
            "6",
            "7",
        ],
        correctAnswer: '6',
        feedback: "It's called 6-String Trivia for a reason!"
    },

    {
        question: "What was Jimi Hendrix's favorite guitar?",
        answerChoices: [
            "Gibson Les Paul",
            "Fender Stratocaster",
            "Twang Machine",
            "Gibson Explorer",
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Fender Stratocaster',
        feedback: "I really should have a tweeter account."
    },

    {
        question: 'A guitar that usually hits the lower tones and most of the time only has 4 strings is called a...',
        answerChoices: [
            "broken guitar.",
            "bass guitar.",
            "keytar.",
            "lower tone guitar.",
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'bass guitar.',
        feedback: "Bears. Beets. Battlestar Galactica."
    },

    {
        question: 'Time to turn it to 11! When was the guitar invented?',
        answerChoices: [
            "1776",
            "2001",
            "1492",
            "1931",
        ],
        correctAnswer: '1931',
        feedback: "Identity theft is not a joke, Jim! Millions of families suffer every year!"
    },

    {
        question: 'Who is the lead guitarist for Led Zeppelin?',
        answerChoices: [
            "Jimmy Page",
            "Slash",
            "BB King",
            "Paul McCartney",
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Jimmy Page',
        feedback: "Blink once if you want me to pull the plug..."
    },

    {
        question: 'What is the standard tuning for a 6 string guitar?',
        answerChoices: [
            "B-B-B-B-B-B",
            "A-B-C-D-E-F",
            "E-A-D-G-B-E",
            "D-A-D-G-B-E",
        ],
        correctAnswer: "E-A-D-G-B-E",
        feedback: "Ryan started the fire!"
    },

    {
        question: 'If you can hear the bass player...',
        answerChoices: [
            "... then turn it up!",
            "... what!??",
            "... bow chk a bow chk a bow bow!",
            "... then he's playing too loud!",
        ],
        correctAnswer: "... then he's playing too loud!",
        feedback: "You couldn't handle my undivided attention."
    },

    {
        question: "What part of the electric guitar picks up the noise from the strings and sends to to the amp?",
        answerChoices: [
            "The bridge",
            "The fret",
            "The pickups",
            "The body",
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'The pickups',
        feedback: "That's why they call it murder and not muckduck."
    },

    {
        question: 'What show were the random quotes from?',
        answerChoices: [
            "The Office",
            "Roseanne",
            "How I Met Your Mother",
            "... Dwight, you ignorant slut!",
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'The Office',
        feedback: "Survey says... The Office!"
    }
];